ACCION International Records MS196
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Communications and External Affairs records, 1950 -- 2012; 1985 -- 2005; MS196.006; 62.7 Linear Feet; 238 Audiovisual Object(s); 365 Digital Object(s)
  - Communication and development files, 1981 -- 2002; MS196.006.002; 14.4 Linear Feet
    - Workshop: Production Capitalizm vs. Financial Capitalizm (Norsk, University of Oslo, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00004; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Instituto Boliviano de Estudios Empresariales (IBEE) Curso de Fondeo - Bolivia, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00005; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Second Annual Seminar on New Development Finance- Frankfurt DAI-IPC Conference, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00006; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Frankfurt [Second Annual Seminar on New Development Finance], 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00007; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Development Finance Leaders Forum - Ford Foundation South Africa, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00008; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Development Finance Leaders Forum - Ford Foundation, South Africa, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00009; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Accion Alumni Reunion - West Denis, 1996; MS196.006.002.006.00010; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
      This Folder is Empty
    - The National Counting on Local Capital Institute - Virginia, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00011; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Comison Presidencial - Venezuela, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00012; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Effective Governance of Microfinance Institutions - Washington, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00013; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Tripartite Mtg on MicroFinance - Lyon, France, 1998; MS196.006.002.006.00014; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Harvard Business School "Corposol Case", 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00015; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Harvard Business School Club Ibero-Americano Latin American business Conference, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00016; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - "Estrategias y Perspectivas en el Umbral del Siglo xxi" - Lima, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00017; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - XII Asamblea General De La FEPCMAC - Cusco, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00018; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Conferencia de Directores de le Red Accion International, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00019; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Conferencia De Directores de La Red Accion International - Bal Harbour, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00020; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Brandeis Univ. Resources of the Poor Experiences with microfinance, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00021; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - New Hampshire College - Microfinance Seminar, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00022; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Meetings of Councils - Cote d'Ivoire, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00023; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Conference on Reality Economics - Boston, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00024; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Seminar on Development Finance - Frankfurt, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00025; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Seminar on Development Finance - Frankfurt, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00026; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - APPAM Conference - Washington, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00027; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Conference Alide-Cartagena, 2000; MS196.006.002.006.00028; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Capital Markets - Credit Enhancement Round Table Conference - Pocantico, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00029; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Mujeres y hombres en el siglo xxi, 1999; MS196.006.002.006.00030; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 6)
    - Communication and development files, 1989 -- 2000; MS196.006.002.088 (Box 88)
    - Communication and development files, 1989 -- 2000; MS196.006.002.089 (Box 89)
  - Vice President of Communications and External Affairs files, 1973 -- 2011; MS196.006.003; 10.8 Linear Feet; 8 Digital Object(s)
    This sub-series contains the working files of the Vice President of Communications and External Affairs. Records were created by vice presidents Robin Ratcliffe (1997-2004) and Bruce MacDonald (2013 on). The files in this subseries relate to the Vice President's work leading the Communications and External Affairs staff. Robin Ratcliffe's files include impact data for use in marketing and promotion, annual financial statements and analysis, notes, planning files for meetings (speaker lists, correspondence, contact lists), partnerships and alliance files (correspondence, marketing, promotion materials), appointment announcements (correspondence, press releases),and planning and correspondence with Hilary Clinton's staff for the First Lady's remarks to the Sixth Conference of Wives of Heads of State and of Governments of the Americas in Bolivia. It also includes pitches or letters sent to potential funders, supporters, magazines, and presidential candidates that promote ACCION from various angles (debt, Chicago, women). It also includes focus group reports, advertisements including spec sheets, ad prices/sizes, ad drafts, marketing plans, brochures, meeting agendas and attendance lists, as well as celebrity partnerships and projects.
    Bruce MacDonald's files include strategic Initiative presentations, conference planning, branding materials, guide for hiring managers, correspondence about branding and conferences, press releases, media contacts, direct mailings, Clinton Global Initiative, Clinton Global Initiative progress reports, statements of commitment, annual report outlines, drafts and notes, media briefing sheets, records relating to Banco Compartamos' initial public offerings including: reports, presentations, correspondence, and its impact on ACCION.
    75 years from the date of creation. 20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
    - Impact Data - Latin America, 1989 -- 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00001; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - L.A. Network - General Info, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00002; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - L.A Monthly Statistics Current Year, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00003; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - UNCTAD Meeting on MicroFM Lyone, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00004; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Inter American Press Association, 1997 -- 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00005; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - UNDP - NetAid, 1999; MS196.006.003.007.00006; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Paella & Picasso, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00007; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - BankBoston Reception, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00008; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Emerging Entrepreneur Award, 1996; MS196.006.003.007.00009; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Emerging Entrepreneur of the Year Award, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00010; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Emerging Entrepreneur of the Year Award, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00011; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - USAID Microenterprise Initiative - DC, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00012; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Latina Excellence Award, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00013; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Parachute Event, 1996; MS196.006.003.007.00014; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Marketing Partners?, 1996 -- 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00015; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Microcredit Summit, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00016; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Basic Marketing Plan, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00017; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Summit, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00018; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Microcredit Summit, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00019; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Microcredit Summit Press, 1999; MS196.006.003.007.00020; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Microcredit Summit Press, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00021; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Results / Microcredit Summit, 1990 -- 1996; MS196.006.003.007.00022; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Microcredit Summit, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00023; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - National Public Radio, 1996; MS196.006.003.007.00024; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Publications Marketing, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00025; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Vista Volunteers - PR, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00026; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Central American Recovery Fund, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00027; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Calvert Pitch, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00028; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Jacques Trigo, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00029; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - London Business School, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00030; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Digital Ambassador, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00031; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Hillary Rodham Clinton, 1995 -- 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00032; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - H. Clinton in Bolivia, 1996; MS196.006.003.007.00033; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - First Lady to South America, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00034; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - U.S. Impact Study Publicity First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00035; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - IDB Awards, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00036; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - U.S. Impact Study, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00037; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Nicaragua, Honduras Delegation, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00038; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - US Delegation San Antonio, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00039; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Press Materials - Delegation Argentina Paraguay, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00040; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Delegation, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00041; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - UN Microloan Report Pitch, 1998; MS196.006.003.007.00042; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Kudos, 1973 -- 1999; MS196.006.003.007.00043; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Hurricane Mitch Pitch, 1999; MS196.006.003.007.00044; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Chicago "Miracle Mile" Pitch, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00045; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Maria Otero Pitch - Women's Magazines, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00046; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Presidential Pitches, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00047; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Debt Pitch, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00048; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Palm Pitch, 1999; MS196.006.003.007.00049; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Bush Microloan Pitch, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00050; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - June 14 Media Event, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00051; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Working Capital Merger, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00052; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Business for Social Responsibility, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00053; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - PR - Beth's Book, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00054; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Vista Commun. Info pack, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00055; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Awareness Campaign, 1997; MS196.006.003.007.00056; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - World Econ Forum, 2002; MS196.006.003.007.00057; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Story Ideas, 1996; MS196.006.003.007.00058; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Microcredit Summit +5, 2002; MS196.006.003.007.00059; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Microcredit Summit 2000, 1999 -- 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00060; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Antenna Group, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00061; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - ACCION USA Marketing Presentations, 2002; MS196.006.003.007.00062; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Talk Radio Training, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00063; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Effective Writing, 2000; MS196.006.003.007.00064; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - New England Media Training, 2002; MS196.006.003.007.00065; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Bridge Fund 1-Pager, 2001; MS196.006.003.007.00066; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 7)
    - Extra Media Training Materials, 2002; MS196.006.003.008.00001; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Vista Media Training, 2002; MS196.006.003.008.00002; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Media Training, 1997 -- 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00003; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Bridge Fund - PR, 1995 -- 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00004; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Atlanta Media Training, 2001; MS196.006.003.008.00005; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Roberta Barnes, 1999 -- 2001; MS196.006.003.008.00006; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Current Photo Needs, 1998 -- 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00007; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Rohanna Mertens, 1999 -- 2002; MS196.006.003.008.00008; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - David Hauser Stock Photography, 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00009; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - ACCION Photography Contract, MS196.006.003.008.00010; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Jessica Boyatt, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00011; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Bob Dowey, 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00012; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Tim Fuller, 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00013; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Beryl Goldberg, 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00014; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Karl Grobl, 2003; MS196.006.003.008.00015; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Judith Haden, 2002; MS196.006.003.008.00016; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Steven Rubin, 2002; MS196.006.003.008.00017; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Potential Photographer - Neeraj Jain, 1996 -- 2003; MS196.006.003.008.00018; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Voices, MS196.006.003.008.00019; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Matting and Dry Mount, MS196.006.003.008.00020; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Photographers, 2001; MS196.006.003.008.00021; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Alex Moral - Photographer, 2003; MS196.006.003.008.00022; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Permission Letters, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00023; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Carol Lundeen, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00024; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Ellie MacDonald, 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00025; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Marta Castellar, 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00026; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Rebecca Janes, 1996 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00027; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Mary Mann, 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00028; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Don West, 1994; MS196.006.003.008.00029; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Photographers Miscellaneous, 1996 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00030; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Stock Photo Suppliers, 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00031; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Printing Vendors, MS196.006.003.008.00032; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Annual Reports - Examples, 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00033; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Hanson Printing, MS196.006.003.008.00034; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Printing Cos, 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00035; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Daniels Printing, 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00036; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Summit Press, 2001; MS196.006.003.008.00037; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Printers Miscellaneous, 1993 -- 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00038; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Strategic Plans and Progress Reports, 1996 -- 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00039; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Brazilian Microfinance, 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00040; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Quantitative Research - Measuring Feasibility of Loan Services for Micorentrepreneurs, 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00041; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Other PR Proposals, 1996; MS196.006.003.008.00042; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Kortenhaus, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00043; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Cause & Effect, 1998 -- 2001; MS196.006.003.008.00044; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Lipman Hearne, 1996 -- 1997; MS196.006.003.008.00045; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Promotion Ideas, 1994; MS196.006.003.008.00046; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Video, 1997 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.008.00047; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Message/Mission - Archive, 1997 -- 1999; MS196.006.003.008.00048; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Mkt. Study Press Release, 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00049; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - U.S. Name/Marketing, 1994 -- 1995; MS196.006.003.008.00050; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - ACCION USA, 2000 -- 2001; MS196.006.003.008.00051; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Atlanta Trip, 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00052; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - Hispanics - USA, 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00053; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - U.S. Network Marketing, 1998 -- 2000; MS196.006.003.008.00054; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 8)
    - U.S. PR Agency, 2000; MS196.006.003.009.00001; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Microfinance Network, 1998; MS196.006.003.009.00002; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Vista- Matt Dunne, 2000; MS196.006.003.009.00003; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - [Business Plan], 2000; MS196.006.003.009.00004; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Amex community Business, 2001; MS196.006.003.009.00005; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - [American Express Small Business Initiative], 2001; MS196.006.003.009.00006; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - AX Project Give Back, 2001; MS196.006.003.009.00007; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - L.A. Network - Tracking Reports, 1989 -- 1991; MS196.006.003.009.00008; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - ACCION Publications - Inside ACCION, 1989 -- 1993; MS196.006.003.009.00009; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - ACCION Alumni Reunion Booklet, 1996; MS196.006.003.009.00010; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - ADEMI (Former Affiliate), 1998; MS196.006.003.009.00011; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Bacno Comunales - Genesis, 1998; MS196.006.003.009.00012; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Bridge Funds, 1995 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.009.00013; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Centro ACCION, 1992; MS196.006.003.009.00014; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Fundusz Micro (Poland), 1997; MS196.006.003.009.00015; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Gateway Fund, 1997; MS196.006.003.009.00016; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Finansol, 1997; MS196.006.003.009.00017; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - FONCAP, 1997 -- 1999; MS196.006.003.009.00018; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Loan Size Issue, 1997 -- 1999; MS196.006.003.009.00019; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Michael Speak (Materials for Writing), 1995 -- 1998; MS196.006.003.009.00020; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - The Microenterprise Policy Training Institute, 1997; MS196.006.003.009.00021; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Profund, 1995 -- 2000; MS196.006.003.009.00022; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)
    - Special Merchant Bank, 1997; MS196.006.003.009.00023; ACCION International (Organization); Ratcliffe, Robin (Box 9)